Privacy Policy

Last update: 01 October 2023

This document entled “Privacy Policy” contains ways of collecng informaon on the User and usage

rights of Parodist Al L.L.C–FZ (hereinaer referred to as the “Rightholder”) (the User is hereinaer also

referred to as “you”) upon uploading, installaon and use of the “Parodist” Mobile Applicaon (hereinaer

referred to as “Mobile App”) by you.

1. General Provisions

1.1. When uploading, installing or using (hereinaer jointly referred to as “use”) the Mobile App, you

agree with the terms and condions of this Privacy Policy in full and give your consent freely, willingly and

in your own interests, to the following methods of Personal Informaon processing procedures: record,

systemazing, storage, adjustment (updang, change), retrieving, usage, transfer (providing, access) to

third pares, including cross-border transmission to the territory of foreign countries, anonymizaon,

blocking, deleng, destrucon for the purposes and according to the procedure provided for herein, using

automaon technologies or without using such technologies.

1.2. This Privacy Policy is an integral part of the documents referring thereto, including the End User

License Agreement for the Mobile App (hereinaer also referred to as the “Agreement”).

1.3. Unless otherwise provided for by this Privacy Policy, the terms and denions used herein shall

have the meaning spulated in the End User License Agreement for the Mobile App.

2. User’s Personal Informaon

2.1. When using the Mobile App as intended, the User does not independently transfer any

informaon on himself/herself to the Rightholder. The Rightholder does not store and does not use the

data allowing to idenfy the User (personal data).

2.2. In this Privacy Policy, the User’s Personal Informaon means:

2.2.1. Data in anonymized form which are automacally transferred when using the Mobile App

depending on soware conguraon of the User, including operang system of the User’s device.

2.2.2. The User understands, accepts and agrees that the Rightholder can use third party soware

in the Mobile App and, therefore, such pares can receive and automacally transfer the anonymized data

(clause 2.2.1 hereof).

This third party soware can include the following systems of collecng and processing analycal data:

• Amplitude, a system collecng and processing data in accordance with the privacy policy put

and/or available in the Internet at: hps://amplitude.com/privacy

• Facebook SDK, a soware of Facebook company, which collects and processes data in accordance

with the data use policy put and/or available in the Internet

at: hps://web.facebook.com/full\_data\_use\_policy

• Firebase, a soware of Google, which collects and processes data in accordance with the data use

policy put and/or available in the Internet at: hps://policies.google.com/privacy

The data being collected using the third party soware, can include:

• data on the User’s device, including unique ideners of the device, its locaon (country, city),

operaon system data (type, version, screen resoluon) etc.;

• request data (me, trac source, IP\-address);

• data on the User’s acons in the Mobile App.

The contents, as well as the condions of collecng and using anonymized data by the rightholders of the

said soware shall be determined directly by such rightholders and regulated by the documents put

and/or available on their sites in the Internet.

By accepng this Privacy Policy and by making certain sengs in his/her soware, including the operang

system of the device, the User agrees with the condions of collecng and using the data by the

rightholders of the above-menoned soware.

2.3. The Rightholder does not verify the authencity of the provided Personal Informaon and the

existence with the User of the necessary consent to its processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy

believing that the User acts in good faith, with due care and makes all necessary eorts to keep this

informaon updated and to receive all the necessary consents of the personal data subjects.

2.4. The Rightholder also collects videos the user records when the user uses the Mobile App, via their

camera or camera roll (if the user has granted the mobile app permission to access their camera or camera

roll). The Rightholder needs it for cases when the user removes the footage from the gallery (photo or

video albums), but they wanted to get it back. So they can easily download this video from the

Rightholder’s cloud storage. Also, this is needed if the user doesn't give the Mobile App permission to

access the gallery (photo or video albums).

2.5. The Rightholder obtains only the specic video the user recorded using the Mobile App; the

Rightholder does not collect user’s photo or video albums even if the user grants their access to them. The

Rightholder encrypt each video that the user uploads using the Mobile App. This means that the only

device that can view the video is the device from which the video was uploaded using the Mobile App –

the user’s device.

2.6. Due to the limited processing resources available on mobile devices, the Rightholder uses third-

party cloud providers – specically, Amazon Web Services – to store videos. The Rightholder uses only

private storage for store users' videos.

2.7. The Rightholder does not disclose user videos to any third pares, except cloud provider Amazon

Web Services (private storage).

3. Purposes of Personal Informaon Processing

3.1. The Rightholder is entled to use the User’s informaon for the following purposes:

3.1.1. ensuring communicaon with the User via the Mobile App for informaon servicing and

markeng;

3.1.2. conducng markeng, stascs and other research based on anonymized data from the

analyc data collecng system indicated in clause 2.3. of the Privacy Policy, in order to improve the Mobile

App;

3.1.3. targeng adversing and/or informaon materials using the data from the analyc data

collecng system indicated in clause 2.3. of the Privacy Policy.

4. Personal Informaon Transfer

4.1. The Rightholder can transfer the User’s informaon to third pares in the following cases:

4.1.1. the User expressed his/her consent to such acons, including cases of the usage by the User

of sengs of the used soware which do not limit providing certain informaon;

4.1.2. such transfer is necessary within the framework of use of the Mobile App’s funconalies

by the User;

4.1.3. in connecon with involving third pares being service providers, for rendering services to

the Rightholder. Personal Informaon is transferred to such service providers with a single purpose

of rendering services to the Rightholder;

4.1.4. in connecon with the use in the Mobile App of third party soware for collecng and

processing the User’s data. In parcular, the Rightholder can use the third party soware in

accordance with clause 2.3. hereof for collecng and processing anonymized data;

4.1.5. in connecon with the transfer of possession, use or ownership of all or part of the assets

of the Rightholder to a third party, including assignment of rights under the contracts concluded with

the User, in favor of such third party;

4.1.6. upon the request of the court or another authorized state authority in the framework of the

procedure provided for by the applicable law;

4.1.7. in order to protect the rights and legal interest of the Rightholder due to violaon of the

contracts concluded with the User.

5. Requirements to Personal Informaon Protecon

5.1. The Rightholder stores the User’s Personal Informaon and ensures its protecon from

unauthorized access and distribuon in accordance with internal rules and regulaons.

5.2. The User’s Personal Informaon is kept condenal.

6. Changing and Deleng Personal Informaon

6.1. Any issues regarding this Privacy Policy, using, changing and deleng the User’s Personal

Informaon or exercising other rights of the User in respect of the Personal Informaon, can be sent to

the Rightholder to the email address indicated in this Privacy Policy.

7. Changing Privacy Policy

7.1. This Privacy Policy can be unilaterally changed or terminated by the Rightholder without preliminary

nocaon of the User. The User is advised to review this Privacy Policy regularly, i.e. its version currently

in force.

7.2. A new Privacy Policy comes into eect from the moment of its placing, unless otherwise provided

for by the new version of the Privacy Policy.

7.3. The current Privacy Policy is located in the Internet at: hps://parodist.ai/polics\_en

Details of the Rightholder:

Parodist Al L.L.C–FZ

Business Center 1, M Floor, The Meydan Hotel, Nad AI, Dubai, UAE.

Email: hello@parodist.ai

Current version of the Privacy Policy dated 1 October 2023.
